[The seeker carefully checks inside]
[But, just leaves?]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps fading away]
[KIM TAE RAE, I found you!]
I found you!
[Screams heard from afar]
Hey!
Hey! Come out
right now!
Let’s go. Let’s go.
Move, move.
[HAO and GYU VIN hides again while someone else is being caught]
[ZHANG HAO, KIM GYU VIN]
Hurry!
[KIM TAE RAE going to prison →]
[ZHANG HAO↑] [KIM GYU VIN↑]
TAE RAE has been captured.
Wait, you’re captured?
Help me!
[At that moment, GYU VIN arrives at the prison with the key]
Save YU JIN!
YU JIN.
[Rescues YU JIN who has been in prison the longest]
Hey, hurry up and come over here.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I really wanted to runaway
but my legs couldn’t move.
[The seeker]
[Water park - SUNG HAN BIN, RICKY]
[The seeker heads to the Water park]
[← SUNG HAN BIN & RICKY]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
Hey, hey!
Isn’t it (the seeker) coming?
[Heads over to HAN BIN and RICKY]
The seeker is nearby.
[Heads inside the supply rental center]
Oh, no.
[← SUNG HAN BIN & RICKY]
(Lights off)
[The seeker →]
[The sound of the seeker’s cane]
[HAN BIN hides in
complete silence]
[The sound of the seeker’s cane getting louder]
[SUNG HAN BIN, I found you!]
Ah, you scared me.
I found you!
Why do you look so scary?
Ah...
Ah, my heart.
[HAN BIN comes out with the seeker]
[RICKY successfully survives]
As expected,
I’m so good.
[Impossible to escape after 20 minutes
JI WOONG checks the remaining time.]
What the?
I was really scared.
We’re in big trouble
if two more people are caught.
We are?
Because 5 people need to be alive in order to win the game.
Ah, really?
- So, that’s why we need the key to save people.
- Yes.
I
will
definitely go and find the keys.
Are you going to leave right now?
[JI WOONG already had a key]
What?!
Hold on.
Hold on a sec.
Don’t leave just now.
Let’s see who comes next
because I also have a key.
- Really?
- Yes.
Wait, you guys both have a key?
I found one, too.
I’m the only one who doesn’t have one?
You do know that
even if you have the key, if you don’t leave
within 20 minutes,
you can’t leave until the game is over.
Okay.
Then, let’s leave
1 minute later.
Good idea.
[Current survivors are 6 people]
[Member’s location]
[RICKY]
[Water park - SEOK MATTHEW, KIM GYU VIN, HAN YU JIN]
[Lobby - ZHANG HAO, PARK GUN WOOK]
[HAO heads to the lobby
[GUN WOOK is also at the lobby]
Oh, you scared me.
Should we hide here?
Can we?
No, no I don’t like it here.
It’s too revealing once you open the door.
[MATTHEW, GYU VIN, YU JIN gathers at the Water park]
Hey!
- What?
- Run, run
Why, why?
On the other side.
It’s over there, it’s over there, it’s over there.
The seeker is coming, coming, coming.
[Hides in Locker Room B]
Run YU JIN! Just run away!
[MATTHEW heads to the lobby]
[The seeker]
The seeker is coming this way.
I hear the seeker’s footsteps!
Where is it coming from?
I don’t know
Hold on.
Where did the seeker go?
Hey, can’t we just fight it and win?
Hey! It’s taller than me.
It’s taller than you?
Similar to you.
I’ll fight it for you.
Where is the exit?
Is this the only exit?
There’s one over there.
Is there one over there, too?
What if the seeker
[The sound of the automatic door opening]
is behind the door?
Why is everyone here?
They were all here this whole time?
Is the seeker gone?
It went out that way.
What are we looking for now?
Where do we need to go?
[Hint for the key]
Did you look here?
I went to the spot next to the ice cream.
I had some ice cream as well.
But it says the key is in this place.
I know where this place is.
It was where I first woke up.
Who’s locked up in prison right now?
HAN BIN, JI WOONG, TAE RAE
Then, are we the only ones alive?
Wait, there was one more person...
Where is RICKY?
We’re  just... staying in this one place...
[The seeker’s scream]
RICKY has been caught.
Has RICKY been caught?
I think so.
No, no, no
It usually screams by itself.
Ah, really?
It was screaming by itself before it tried to catch me.
Shouldn’t we head for the ice cream spot? Ice cream?
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps getting closer]
[All the members runs to Locker Room B]
Run, runaway!
[Meanwhile, in the supply rental center where RICKY is hiding]
I like it here.
I found the ice cream spot.
[Hint for the key]
The key is in here?
Hey!
In the ice!
It’s inside the ice.
Ah, how are we going to melt it?
[Finds the key inside the ice]
[GUN WOOK heads to the Sauna]
[Hint for the key]
I'll stand guard.
[Carefully searches the human figure from the hint]
Did you find it?
No.
[Fails to find the key and leaves]
Hey!
It’s coming! Hey, it’s coming!
[All the members gathered at Locker Room B]
[Heads to the Water park after hearing the seeker]
Hey, where is the ice?
The ice?
I gave it to GYU VIN.
Put the ice in the water.
Is it hot water?
It won’t make any noise if we break it in the water.
Ah, you’re right.
[The sound of breaking the ice]
It’s broken, broken, broken.
No, it’s just the light from the key chain.
[There’s only a key chain but not the key?]
[← The key]
[It sank underwater once the ice broke]
Oh! The seeker is coming.
It’s over there?
[HAO and GYU VIN heads to Locker Room B again]
[ZHANG HAO, KIM GYU VIN]
[SEOK MATTHEW, HAN YU JIN]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
[The seeker appears]
[SEOK MATTHEW, HAN YU JIN] [ZHANG HAO, KIM GYU VIN]
[The seeker]
[↑ ZHANG HAO]
[Spots HAO running to the Water park]
[PARK GUN WOOK →]
Huh, what the?
[← HAN YU JIN] [SEOK MATTHEW ↓] [ZHANG HAO →]
[SEOK MATTHEW ↓]
[The seeker →]
[The seeker was one step behind]
[HAO heads to the supply rental center]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps wandering around]
Who is it?
It’s me!
Okay, okay.
[Phone alarm]
Later, once the play time is
2,222 seconds, the seeker will suddenly disappear
and you will have 4 minutes to hide yourself again.
But this time hide yourself very well.
The 4 minutes will start when the ‘hide-and-seek’ song begins.
Within 4 minutes, you can not go save your team members.
After 4 minutes, there will be two seekers. So, good luck hiding.
The key. 4 minutes.
Weren’t there two seekers already??
Hey, you told me you saw two seekers?
Yeah, I’m pretty sure I saw two seekers.
[Remaining time]
[At the same time, in the snack bar]
[※ Filmed with prior permission]
Oh my god.
Let’s give some ice cream to them.
What is this?
Where did you get all of these?
Thank you, MATTHEW.
MATTHEW is giving out free food.
This prison has some good food.
[The seeker disappears]
[4 minutes of free time]
[MATTHEW and GYU VIN meets at the Water park]
It’s pretty deep...
What?
Did you drop it here?
Is the key in there?
Hey, it’s super deep.
[← The fallen key
from the ice]
You have to get wet no matter what.
Okay, why not?
[Puts out his arm to reach for the key]
Can you just hold this?
Go, go, go!
I can’t reach it. I can’t reach it.
Ah, hold on.
What should we do?
Let’s go find something
long to use.
How about you go look for something else.
Okay!
[Hint for the key]
Then wait, let me go to the sauna room
and find the key.
RICKY, RICKY!
Let’s go! Now!
We only have 4 minutes left.
What are you going to do?
Right now, we have 4 minutes.
I know, I know. So, what are we going to do?
You don’t have a key, right?
Yup!
Let’s go find the key!
Ha.. my legs are killing me.
[GYU VIN is still struggling to find the keys]
[Decides to dive in]
Hey, GYU VIN!
Did you really go in?
To find the key?
Yeah.
Did you find it?
I did.
You’re insane.
[KIM GYU VIN finds the key]
Hey, TAE RAE!
Yes?
How many seconds are left in the timer?
Ah, you have to check that?
Yup.
I have 4 minutes left.
4 minutes?
[KIM JI WOONG - order of capture: 1] [SUNG HAN BIN - order of capture: 3]
[KIM TAE RAE - order of capture: 2]
You have to leave now, TAE RAE.
You have to leave right now.
You’re going to be locked up if you don’t leave.
But, can you really
[HAN BIN confuses the order of capture ]
hide well?
Hey, I’m pretty quick.
You leave first.
I'm the one who has the most time.
[Actually, JI WOONG has the least amount of time]
[TAE RAE rescued by HAN BIN’s key]
[A few moments later]
[The gatekeeper approaching JI WOONG]
Why?
Has it been 20 minutes?
[Has it been 20 minutes already?]
Ah! It seems that it was delayed because the timer stopped.
[A few minutes back]
Don’t forget to check the time.
What is the time difference between us?
How many minutes do you have left?
The timer was paused.
[JI WOONG accidently stopped the timer]
[The actual time and the timer’s time was different]
[Exceeded 20 minutes,
KIM JI WOONG can not escape from prison]
But, I didn’t press the stop button.
This is so unfair.
Ready or not,
here I come.
[As the 4 minutes are coming to a close]
[HAO heads to the storage room in the cafeteria]
Oh my god.
[RICKY heads to the supply rental center again]
[Uses the tubes to hide himself properly]
Ready or not,
here I come.
I found it.
[PARK GUN WOOK finds the key (in the human figure)]
Huh! What happened?
Oh, no!
Hey, did you go in the water?
HAN BIN, please.
[GYU VIN saves SUNG HAN BIN with his key]
I found it. x4
[HAN YU JIN finds the key (inside the microwave)]
Ready or not,
two seekers are coming to get you.
[After escaping,
HAN BIN hides under a bench in Locker Room B]
I should’ve ran away further. Ah...
[MATTHEW hides in the playroom on the 1st floor Sauna]
It’s coming. x3
[↑ KIM TAE RAE] [PARK GUN WOOK ↓]
[TAE RAE and GUN WOOK are at the small pool on the 1st floor Water park]
[YU JIN is at the playroom on the 2nd floor Water park]
What should I do?
I can’t leave.
Are you done hiding?
I’m coming to get you, again!
[Hide-and-seek restart]
Ah, time is up.
I think the two seekers are going to come in any second!
The two seekers
[KIM TAE RAE ↓] [PARK GUN WOOK ↓]
I just came out of prison.
Anyhow, I’m safe for now.
Nothing seems to be easy.
[GUN WOOK is located at the small pool on the 1st floor]
[YU JIN heads to the 2nd floor playroom]
[HAN YU JIN →]
[PARK GUN WOOK ↑]
GUN WOOK!
Why did you come here?
[The sound of PARK GUN WOOK breathing]
It’s really hot here.
Because it's humid here.
[↑ PARK GUN WOOK] [HAN YU JIN →]
[Member’s location]
[8 remaining survivors and 4 keys left]
[← The seeker] [The seeker →]
[The seeker checks the Sauna]
[SEOK MATTHEW →]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
[The seeker ↓] [SEOK MATTHEW →]
[Turns its direction and heads to the lobby outside]
I’m scared.
[The second seeker is at the Water park]
[2nd floor] [← PARK GUN WOOK] [HAN YU JIN →]
[1st floor] [← KIM TAE RAE]
Please save me.
I can’t get caught again.
Please, please.
[The seeker heads to the 2nd floor playroom]
Please.
[Before the seeker arrives,
YU JIN moves inside the playroom]
[← HAN YU JIN]
[← The seeker]
[The sound of the seeker’s cane]
Please.
[The seeker →]
Don’t come near me. x2
[Finds YU JIN who was hiding]
[HAN YU JIN →]
[Trying desperately to run away]
I’m sorry. x2
[HAN YU JIN, I found you!]
I’m sorry, I’m sorry!!
I found you!
Okay, okay.
YU JIN was taken away right in front of me.
Earlier, JI WOONG was taken away in front of me.
But because I have a key,
I’ll go rescue YU JIN.
GUN WOOK to the rescue. x2
[GUN WOOK waving at someone]
[← ???]
[← PARK GUN WOOK]
Who is that?
You’re alive? I saw you get caught.
I was saved by my key.
Oh, really?
[YU JIN arrived in prison]
Who is that?
I didn’t have any energy left to run away.
I have a key.
[Opens the lock with the key he had]
I unlocked it.
[YU JIN, released after 1 minute of being locked away in prison]
I was on my way to rescue you. Who else is locked up?
Only JI WOONG.
Then, I guess everyone is alive.
But, I have no clue where the rest of the people are hiding.
[← RICKY]
[In the dark supply rental center]
I really like this hiding spot.
I will trust this hiding spot
because I worked hard to make it.
[← ZHANG HAO]
[The seeker heads to HAO’s hiding spot]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
[But, just leaves]
I really want to come out but
the seeker keeps on coming here.
Even though I want to move around, there are two seekers now, so I can’t.
If one (seeker) leaves, the second one appears.
I miss my mom. x2
[SUNG HAN BIN, KIM GYU VIN]
[Locker Room B]
[← SUNG HAN BIN]
I guess they can’t see here.
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
[← The seeker]
[← KIM GYU VIN]
I hear footsteps.
[SUNG HAN BIN →]
[Finds GYU VIN]
What was that?
[GYU VIN running away]
[ and the seeker chasing after him]
[KIM GYU VIN, I found you!]
[The seeker looks again in Locker Room B]
Ah, please.
I don’t want to be caught again.
[← SUNG HAN BIN]
[SUNG HAN BIN, I found you!]
How did they find me?
[Meanwhile in the Sauna, YU JIN is figuring out the seeker’s location]
[Rustling sound]
What are you doing?
MATTHEW?
Yes.
I was here.
The seeker is over there.
It’s coming, it’s coming.
[← The seeker] [SEOK MATTHEW & HAN YU JIN ↓]
It’s over there.
[The seeker follows them to Locker Room B]
[The second seeker heads to Locker Room B as well]
[← SEOK MATTHEW]
Ah, I’m so scared.
Ahh~
Okay, okay
[SEOK MATTHEW, I found you!]
Okay,
I’m sorry.
Was I too obvious?
[Phone alarm]
The remaining time is 444 seconds.
The seeker’s shadows, quicker than the seekers,
are on their way to find you.
The seeker’s shadows arrive
along with a disturbing noise.
So, try not to get caught.
What...
does that mean?
I... don’t understand.
[(Using a translator)]
Oh~!
'敏捷' (Quick)
Please don’t use these kinds of words.
They could’ve just said a ‘fast-moving’ seeker
How was I supposed to know that hard word?
[The ‘fast-moving’ shadows are on their way ]
[The sound of the shadows moving]
What is that?
The shadows are moving in twos?
Or is it in threes?
[The shadows are heading to the Water park
where TAE RAE and RICKY are hiding]
[The sound of the shadows moving]
(Lights off)
The shadows won’t be able to find me.
[← RICKY]
I picked a good hiding spot.
[The shadows are heading in TAE RAE’s direction]
[← KIM TAE RAE]
[ The roar of the shadows]
Wow, what is that?
[TAE RAE, running away from the shadows]
[KIM TAE RAE →]
[The shadows are chasing after TAE RAE]
[KIM TAE RAE ↓]
[Successfully, ran away from the shadows]
[Enters the cafeteria to look for places to hide]
I almost got caught just now.
There were even 4 shadows.
[Remaining time]
I...
will save HAN BIN.
Right now? No!
Maybe a little later.
No HAN BIN, you can do it.
Okay, I’ll try to stay alive.
[With only 200 seconds remaining, HAN BIN is rescued]
[HAN BIN hides in the towel bin in Locker Room B]
[The seeker appears right after HAN BIN hides]
This doesn't look good.
How many minutes do we have remaining?
I want to get out.
1 minute remaining.
1 minute?
Do we win if we hold out for 1 minute?
[The seekers and the shadows hurry to find the members]
[PARK GUN WOOK →]
[PARK GUN WOOK]
[The seeker]
[GUN WOOK and the seeker are getting closer]
[Passing each other by a whisker]
[PARK GUN WOOK →]
[The seeker chases right after it notices him]
[End of hide-and-seek]
I can’t find you.
Nightingale.
I can’t find you. Nightingale.
[After the game ended,
the members gathered near the prison]
What the?!
You’re still alive, right?
- Finally!
- Isn’t the survival rate more than 50%?
- It’s finally over.
- Right.
HAN BIN, how was it?
Wasn’t it fun?
The seeker passed me 4 four times.
Wow...
I was hiding in the swimming pool
and 4 shadows started to come and surround me.
Ahh~~
[RICKY, who was never caught, joins the members]
Hey RICKY, where were you hiding?
He (RICKY) was really just quietly hiding.
You never got caught?
Yup, I never got caught.
I had some tubes so I hid very well.
But it seems like we won.
[With the survival rate of 66.7%,
ZEROSE receives the prize]
We did it. x2
Barely.
It was much scarier than I thought.
That’s true. I almost.
Like
you can’t compare it to anything.
[The roar of the shadows]
I found you guys.
Don’t go.
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]